

Anas Hussein Joudeh

anasjoudeh51@gmail.com | M+ 962785166506

Nationality: Jordanian
 Languages: Arabic & English
 Date of Birth: 24th July, 1988
 Marital Status: Married

Current Location: Amman -JordanHome Location: Amman -Jordan

• Current employer: Marriott international St Regis Hotel

• Reason for move? New opportunity

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Every brand has stories to tell—stories that will not only engage, surprise, delight, its exceed more than that it's all about connect and how to win the hearts of everyone around you by give them the support they need by feeling and listening to them and knowing how you can make them every day work from their hearts and not leaving them for the failure.

I Anas Joudeh 33 years old , I've joined the Residences at the St. Regis Amman as a Senior Butler /head Butler on the 3rd of Dec 2017 . And some of my role is Oversee and supervise the duties and functions of the Residence Executive. Coordinate with residences team, Concierge, Butler Supervisor, Front Engineering team, Housekeeping and the other third parties team where necessary. Answer all residents' questions regarding Residence & hotel facilities and points of interest and maximize revenue (Residential Services) where possible, through upselling of the hotel facilities and outlets. As well. since that day until present it's make me every day learn something new in our career path and closer to my goals where starting from supporting our team ,anticipate the guests needs not only that, but beyond that much further, that what give me the power and gives me the greatest motivation to continue to succeed until to be a successful leader and all those talented around me are successful. I have a strong personality in dealing with others and in very calm way ,I'm well organised and highly motivated person professional and my guests satisfaction are always on top of my responsibilities and priorities , I have strong leadership where I can balance between my responsibilities and every day is a great challenging day to use my skills to reach my goals .

EXPERIENCE

Senior Butler -Acting as Residences Supervisor (Opening)

Marriott international - St. Regis Amman - Amman, Jordan | December 2017 - Current

Senior Butler -Acting as Residences Supervisor: 7th Dec -July (Pre- Opening)

Marriott international - St. Regis Amman - Amman, Jordan | December 2017 - July 2018

Fairmont Gold Supervisor

Fairmont Amman (Fairmont hotels& resorts) - Amman, Jordan | October 2016 - November 2017

Concierge Team Leader

Al Faisaliah Hotel a Rosewood hotels &resorts - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia | December 2013 - May 2016

Senior Butler

Al Faisaliah Hotel a Rosewood hotels & resorts - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia | December 2011 - December 2013

Telephone Operator

Kempinski Hotel Ishtar Dead Sea - Sweimah -Dead sea , Jordan | September 2010 - November 2011

Kempinski Hotel Ishtar Dead Sea - Sweimah -Dead sea , Jordan | July 2007 - January 2009

Concierge Agent

Land mark Amman hotel & Conference Centre - Amman - April 2005 - June 2006

EDUCATION

75 Al Muqableen & Um qsiar High School | Amman, Jordan | July 2006

SKILLS

- PMS: Excellent User for (Opera, Fidelio MS Office: very Good User for (Excel, System, micros system)
 - Microsoft Word, PowerPoint...etc).
- Excellent user for Go concierge system
- Excellent user for Building link software
 Excellent user for fax's copiers and (official resident website)
 - printers, scanner.
- Internet Excellent user.

TRAINING SKILLS & ONLINE COURSES & CERTIFICATES

- -Culture Awareness
- -Rosewood Standards Specialist (Train-the-Trainer)
- -Fairmont Hotels& resorts- (Train the Trainer)
- -Guest Recovery Handling the complaint
- -Team work
- -Fire evacuation and extinguishing course
- -Kempinski DNA about (Passion for Luxury/Creating Traditions People-Oriented/Straightforwardness

Entrepreneurial Performance

- -Butler Foundation Program from Robert Watson's (Guild of professional English Butler)
- -Harvard Manage Mentor level one
- -TOPPS training St. Regis hotel, Marriott international.
- -7 star Butler Service Skills & Knowledge all levels 1-4
- -ESSM training (Essential skills for Supervisors & Managers).